Find your magic
Upside-Down Magic is a fantasy, family, tv movie film directed by Joe Nussbaum.
Nory and her best friend Reina enter the Sage Academy for Magical Studies, where Nory’s
unconventional powers land her in a class for those with wonky, or “upside-down,” magic.
Undaunted, Nory sets out to prove that that upside-down
magic can be just as powerful as right-side-up.
Nory Boxwood Horace, played by Izabela Rose.
Reina Carvajal, played by Siena Agudong.
Budd Skriff, played by Kyle Howard.
Andres Padillo, played by Max Torina.
Elliot Cohen, played by Elie Samouhi.
Pepper Phan, played by Alison Fernández.
Upside-Down Magic is a 2020 American fantasy film
released as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
It is an adaptation of the eponymous fantasy book series by
Sarah Mlynowski, Lauren Myracle, and Emily Jenkins.
The film stars Izabela Rose and Siena Agudong and co-starring Vicki Lewis.
It premiered on Disney Channel on July 31, 2020.
The film explores themes of friendship, magic,
supernatural, young heroes, good versus evil.